#WordList18
exaggerate
examine
exchange
exclude
executive
exert
exist
existence
exotic
expand
expansion
expect
expectation
expression
extent
extension
extensive
extinguish
excerpt
exquisite
exempt
exclaim
experience
experiment
expert
expire
exploit
explore
export
expose
extinct
explode
excel
decade
spy
cast
zeal
claim
acclaim
vibrate
brilliant
navigation
stern
therapy
fabric
robust
vague
contrast
contradict
instinct
mortgage
prone
confuse
paragraph
industrial
judicial
marginal
accidental
spiral
decimal
plural
occasional
disposal
feudal
appraisal
material