#WordList1
compel
impulse
repel
compulsory
anniversary
annual
sophisticated
philosopher
realistic
tribute
attribute
contribute
facilitate
facility
factor
affair
normalization
abnormal
variety
various
variable
invariable
profound
fundamental
exposure
failure
pressure
nurture
procedure
gradual
graduate
upgrade
aggressive
congress
depend
independent
suspend
compensate
indispensable
ponder
pension
polite
policy
political
politician
metropolitan
saddle
assess
conscious
dubious
mysterious
obvious
serious
religious
ambiguous
ambitious
anxious
cautious
notorious
spacious
tedious
vicious
monotonous
continuous
homogeneous
conspicuous
strenuous
gorgeous
marvellous
fabulous
rigorous
spontaneous
tremendous
defendant
elegant
ignorant
relevant
tolerant
fragrant
arrogant
malignant
redundant
peasant
accountant
militant
upset
setback
settlement