#WordList13
insult
segregate
urban
territory
nerve
tremble
lateral
sacred
sacrifice
provide
evident
invisible
envisage
revise
plateau
monopoly
origin
original
originate
educate
evaluate
escalate
effective
efficient
efficiency
estate
establish
statement
statesman
static
stale
stalk
stable
consist
resist
warmth
youth
accurate
accuracy
curious
current
currency
incur
occur
occurrence
corridor
secure
security
stability
liability
frigid
domestic
domain
operate
operator
operational
embed
embezzle
embody
embrace
emphasis
emphasize
engage
engagement
enable
encounter
enforce
enhance
enlarge
entail
embark
enthusiasm
entitle
endow
endure
employee
endeavour
endorse
inertia