#WordList7
trivial
tribe
senior
evade
option
optional
attach
detach
negative
neglect
negligible
negotiate
store
nationality
native
natural
subscribe
prescribe
prescription
describe
verge
converge
susceptible
sustain
qualitative
passion
passive
commute
contest
gene
general
generate
generation
generous
genius
genre
generalize
genuine
prior
prime
primary
premier
unusual
visual
casual
individual
mutual
punctual
prospect
suspect
prospective
respective
retrospect
perspective
specialize
specific
species
despise
speculate
monument
common
abstract
contract
extract
subtract
trace
track
trait
trigger
portray
wedding
setting
striking
finding
fitting
following
leading
glowing
fertile
juvenile
hostile
reptile
fragile
futile