#WordList11
compile
lofty
bureaucracy
complex
perplex
democracy
democratic
epidemic
gracious
congratulate
gratitude
scarcely
seemingly
barely
critic
critical
criterion
crisis
jury
adjust
justice
justify
severe
proper
property
incorporate
corporation
denote
notion
notable
noticeable
survive
vital
vivid
revive
vigorous
design
significant
significance
assign
resign
aesthetic
census
plea
plead
simplicity
international
interior
internal
interfere
intellectual
category
catastrophe
casualty
incidence
suicide
activate
alternate
candidate
certificate
cultivate
estimate
fabricate
fascinate
formulate
fortunate
illustrate
imitate
terminate
tolerate
frustrate
simulate
alienate
articulate
saturate
desperate
agitate
penetrate
nominate
evaporate
stimulate
assassinate
circulate
lubricate
deteriorate