#WordList15
forecast
foremost
foresee
locate
location
allocate
endurance
durable
startle
sparkle
penalty
component
postpone
tangle
frequent
intimate
press
suppress
compress
depress
impression
repression
oppress
sue
sequence
consequence
subsequent
appreciate
precious
vocal
rate
transcend
ascend
withdraw
withhold
atmosphere
merit
tune
revelation
tempo
adequate
equator
equivalent
psychology
sociology
technology
testimony
import
infer
independence
indignant
inevitable
innocent
intensive
insidious
ingenious
inhabit
intricate
intrigue
invalid
impair
implication
immediate
indicate
investigate
object
objection
obstacle
obstruct
opponent
oppose
auction
collision
nutrition
sanction
division
illusion
obsession
meditation
orientation
temptation
association
duration
indication
innovation
operation
organization
recreation