#WordList5
mixture
heritage
inherit
circumstance
cardinal
calculate
reputation
dispute
compute
linguistic
journal
cycle
quantitative
thrust
obsolete
sphere
victim
awkward
outward
upward
reward
award
synthetic
acquisition
questionnaire
conquer
acquire
require
requirement
voluntary
volunteer
surrender
decrease
increase
create
creative
concrete
constrain
restrain
restrict
syndrome
transaction
transfer
transform
translation
transplant
transmit
transparent
transistor
transition
submit
substitute
subtle
subordinate
suburb
subsidy
substantial
alien
enlighten
loosen
strengthen
weaken
wooden
threaten
abolish
accomplish
astonish
cherish
distinguish
flourish
nourish
polish
publish
selfish
morality
speciality
personality
vulgar