#WordList19
dictate
indicative
index
predict
verdict
emotion
motivate
remote
dental
maximum
phrase
orthodox
avail
available
valuable
triumph
conscientious
ruin
elaborate
collaborate
narrative
vessel
counterpart
solemn
coward
response
sponsor
correspond
spouse
harness
witness
capable
conceive
concept
conception
exceptional
captive
capture
escape
deceive
occupy
anticipate
chase
recovery
principle
principal
participate
harassment
temperament
ornament
management
appointment
argument
entertainment
government
investment
payment
comment
mention
mental