#WordList12
initial
initiate
initiative
vehicle
remove
abundant
abundance
linger
optimum
optimistic
confidence
confidence
confidential
federal
federation
mislead
practice
practical
practitioner
integrate
integrity
coherent
adhere
cohesive
hesitate
ideology
conduct
deduct
deduce
productive
extravagant
extreme
immune
community
municipal
communicate
communication
magnify
magnificent
magnitude
petition
alter
alternative
temper
waterproof
proof
evolve
involve
revolve
revolt
volume
legal
legislation
legitimate
delegate
allege
ensure
insure
insurance
surname
surpass
surplus
survival
surge
coincide
coincidence
confirm
competent
comprehend
concentrate
council
court
comprise
commence
conceal
concise
consult
consecutive
conspiracy
contemplate
coordinate
colleague
contaminate
coalition
combine
compete